seotrafficspider.com 2015-05-21

# SEO Traffic Spider | Privacy Policy | Targeted Website Traffic | Affordable SEO Services | Website Traffic | SEO Services | Increase Website Traffic | SEO Packages

|   
---  
|   
---  
|  |   
---  
|  |   
---|---  

|   
---  
  
The Internet today has become a remarkable and also an indispensable tool. It can change the way people live and one can experience that potential today. People can converse with each other, purchase products and services, watch news, and do many more things now with just a few clicks. Therefore, it is crucial for SEO Traffic Spider to retain its customers privacy when they make use of what the Internet has to offer.

SEOtrafficspider.com is a website owned by Bellamonte Nash Outsourcing. This privacy policy contains Bellamonte Nash Outsourcing’s policy on collection and usage of your personal information.

You can visit SEO Traffic Spider website without revealing or disclosing any personal information. However, there may be times when we may require information from you. We consider your business to be solely yours and no one else’s. Your privacy is important to us and therefore we will take all the precaution and measures to protect the information that you share with us. In order to protect data and customer’s privacy, SEO Traffic Spider follows guidelines and principles according to world wide practices.   

|   | We do not sell or give out your personal details like name, email address, postal address, phone number, or any other information to anyone.  
---|---  
   
|   | We use stringent measures to protect all your information from any unauthorized users.  
---|---  
NOTICE  
We will approach you when we require any personal information that personally identifies you or enables us to get in touch with you. Usually, this information is required when you register on our site or download any software, order newsletters, enter into a contest, make payment for our services that your hire, generate leads and referrals or optionally fill in any form on our website. We make use of your information that personally identifies you for four main reasons:  

1\. To make it easy for you to use our website so that you do not have to enter your information more than one time.

2\. To aid you in quickly finding services, packages, offers or information.

3\. To create the most relevant content for you.

4\. To alert you about our service upgrades, new offers, new packages, information updates and other latest services from SEO Traffic Spider.  

Any partners or resources listed on SEO Traffic Spider may ask you for your personal information when you click on any links that link to them from our website. Though we make it a point to link to reputed firms only, we cannot exercise any control on their usage of your personal information. Therefore, we encourage you to read and understand privacy policies of such websites and trust them before disclosing your personal data.  

CONSENT  

If you do not wish to provide your personal information or register with us, you will not have access to areas requiring registration.

If you choose to register with us, you can select the types of information that you would like to receive from us through subscription to various services. If you do not wish to receive any information regarding SEO Traffic Spider services, events, programs, or offers by either email or postal mail, you can let us know and we will respect your decision.  

SECURITY  

SEO Traffic Spider takes strong measures for the protection of your privacy and ensures that your personal information is only used for the purpose it is intended. We take every precaution for the protection of your data from any misuse, loss, unauthorized access or any alteration, disclosure, or destruction.

We never share your personal information outside our company without your approval. Within the company, data is stored in servers that are password controlled and that have limited access. Your processes can be stored and processed for use in India or other countries where SEO Traffic Spider has its subsidiaries located.

You also have an important role in safeguarding your information. No one can access your personal information to view or edit it, unless they know your username and passcode. Therefore, you must not disclose or share these with others.  

COOKIES  

The use of cookies will be purely for statistical purposes, market research, or to help you navigate and use our site with ease. Any personal information will not be used for this process.  

NOTICE TO PARENTS  
   
It is important that you also protect your children’s privacy. Although SEO Traffic Spider does not contain any content that is targeted towards children, we always encourage you to speak to your children about the responsible use of any information that personally identifies them while making use of the Internet.  
   
ENFORCEMENT  

Any information that you provide to us including your name and email address is used to send you any updates regarding our services, customer satisfaction surveys, new service announcements, special offers, and also to keep you updated on the daily progress of your campaign. When you sign in to any of our packages, you will be required to enter your credit card number and other personal information for billing purposes. We will use this information only for billing of the services we will provide to you at that time.

SEO Traffic Spider does not rent, give out, or sell your personal information outside the company or with companies not affiliated to us, except to provide services requested by you. With your approval, we may transfer your information if at any time there is an acquisition or merger of SEO Traffic Spider with another company.

However, SEO Traffic Spider may, without notice, disclose your personal information only if it is required by law. Such information can also be disclosed in good faith when it is necessary to:  

|   | adhere to the order of the law or comply with legal proceedings served on SEO Traffic Spider or its parent company.  
---|---  
   
|   | safeguard the property and rights of SEO Traffic Spider and its related websites and the parent company.  
---|---  

|   |  act in urgent situations for protecting the personal safety of the users of SEO Traffic Spider, its related websites, or the public.  
---|---  

Lastly, SEO Traffic Spider reserves the right to alter or edit its privacy policy at any time. When such changes are made, we will notify this on our website.  
  
  |   |    
  |  |    
  |  |    
  |  |
